let questionStore = [
  [
    {
      answer: [2, 11, 10, 4, 7, 8, 3],
      stem: '请从以下十二个字中，识别一句七言唐诗。',
      options: [
        '借',
        '处',
        '夜',
        '家',
        '淮',
        '问',
        '杏',
        '近',
        '酒',
        '何',
        '秦',
        '泊',
      ],
      img: null,
      no: 1,
    },
    {
      answer: [6, 2, 5, 0, 8],
      stem: '请从以下九个字中，识别一句五言唐诗。',
      options: ['山', '平', '日', '客', '随', '依', '白', '楼', '尽'],
      img: null,
      no: 2,
    },
    {
      answer: [0, 8, 3, 1, 7],
      stem: '请从以下九个字中，识别一句五言唐诗。',
      options: ['花', '多', '又', '知', '逢', '时', '雨', '少', '落'],
      img: null,
      no: 3,
    },
    {
      answer: [6, 9, 0, 3, 11, 4, 10],
      stem: '请从以下十二个字中，识别一句七言唐诗。',
      options: [
        '愿',
        '身',
        '无',
        '作',
        '翼',
        '彩',
        '在',
        '风',
        '双',
        '天',
        '鸟',
        '比',
      ],
      img: null,
      no: 4,
    },
    {
      answer: [1, 6, 4, 8, 5],
      stem: '请从以下九个字中，识别一句五言唐诗。',
      options: ['长', '前', '月', '安', '见', '人', '不', '云', '古'],
      img: null,
      no: 5,
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      answer: [0, 6, 8, 11, 3, 9, 4],
      stem: '请从以下十二个字中，识别一句七言唐诗。',
      options: [
        '飞',
        '江',
        '芳',
        '三',
        '尺',
        '逢',
        '流',
        '绕',
        '直',
        '千',
        '宛',
        '下',
      ],
      img: null,
      no: 1,
    },
    {
      answer: [0, 5, 9, 2, 11, 6, 1],
      stem: '请从以下十二个字中，识别一句七言唐诗。',
      options: [
        '醉',
        '笑',
        '场',
        '出',
        '尺',
        '卧',
        '莫',
        '仰',
        '门',
        '沙',
        '大',
        '君',
      ],
      img: null,
      no: 2,
    },
    {
      answer: [3, 0, 4, 8, 7],
      stem: '请从以下九个字中，识别一句五言唐诗。',
      options: ['春', '色', '锦', '江', '入', '天', '地', '年', '旧'],
      img: null,
      no: 3,
    },
    {
      answer: [6, 8, 5, 2, 4],
      stem: '请从以下九个字中，识别一句五言唐诗。',
      options: ['一', '白', '青', '鹭', '天', '上', '难', '解', '于'],
      img: null,
      no: 4,
    },
    {
      answer: [5, 11, 2, 8, 7, 9, 0],
      stem: '请从以下十二个字中，识别一句七言唐诗。',
      options: [
        '花',
        '堪',
        '犹',
        '日',
        '须',
        '隔',
        '开',
        '后',
        '唱',
        '庭',
        '直',
        '江',
      ],
      img: null,
      no: 5,
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      answer: [5, 2, 11, 0, 10, 1, 4],
      stem: '请从以下十二个字中，识别一句七言唐诗。',
      options: [
        '于',
        '月',
        '叶',
        '满',
        '花',
        '霜',
        '乌',
        '烟',
        '天',
        '啼',
        '二',
        '红',
      ],
      img: null,
      no: 1,
    },
    {
      answer: [1, 3, 4, 6, 5],
      stem: '请从以下九个字中，识别一句五言唐诗。',
      options: ['舟', '行', '万', '到', '水', '处', '穷', '送', '故'],
      img: null,
      no: 2,
    },
    {
      answer: [1, 10, 6, 4, 9, 3, 11],
      stem: '请从以下十二个字中，识别一句七言唐诗。',
      options: [
        '闻',
        '忽',
        '声',
        '风',
        '夜',
        '水',
        '一',
        '琵',
        '琶',
        '春',
        '如',
        '来',
      ],
      img: null,
      no: 3,
    },
    {
      answer: [3, 7, 1, 5, 2],
      stem: '请从以下九个字中，识别一句五言唐诗。',
      options: ['飞', '鸟', '心', '恨', '千', '惊', '拜', '别', '绝'],
      img: null,
      no: 4,
    },
    {
      answer: [1, 7, 10, 4, 9, 6, 3],
      stem: '请从以下十二个字中，识别一句七言唐诗。',
      options: [
        '月',
        '曾',
        '明',
        '水',
        '海',
        '泪',
        '为',
        '经',
        '上',
        '难',
        '沧',
        '珠',
      ],
      img: null,
      no: 5,
    },
  ],
];

export default questionStore;
